《终结者3：机器的觉醒》
未来尚未发生
The future has not been written.
命运要靠自己创造
There is no fate but what we mak e for ourselves.
真希望我能相信这句话
I wish I could believe that.
我叫约翰康纳
My name is John Connor.
我出生前他们就想杀我
They tried to murder me before I was born.
他们在我十三岁那年也试过
When I was 13, they tried again.
来自未来的机器人
Machines from the future.
魔鬼终结者
Terminators.
从小我妈就说大灾难即将来临
All my life, my mother told me the storm was coming.
- 最后审判日 - 康纳！
- Judgment Day. - Connor!
人类与机器的大战
The beginning of a war between man and machines.
三十亿人口一瞬间被消灭
Three billion lives would vanish in an instant.
我将率领人类获得最后胜利
And I would lead what was left of the human race to ultimate victory.
这一天还没来临
It hasn't happened.
核弹没有从空而降
No bombs fell.
电脑也没有控制世界
Computers didn't tak e control.
我们阻止了审判日
We stopped Judgment Day.
我应该感到安全…
I should feel safe…
但是却没有
…but I don't.
我决定彻底脱离社会
So I live off the grid.
没有电话 住址
No phone, no address.
没有人或东西找得到我
No one and nothing can find me.
我断绝和过去的联系
I've erased all connections to the past.
但是我再努力…
But as hard as I try…
也无法停止做梦…
…I can't erase my dreams…
可怕的噩梦
…my nightmares.
沉重的未来压得我喘不过气
I feel the weight of the future bearing down on me.
我不想要的未来
A future I don't want.
于是我一直逃跑…
So I k eep running…
拚命地逃跑
…as fast as I can.
任何地方
Anywhere.
越远越好
Nowhere.
（比佛利山庄）
天啊
Oh, my God.
你没事吧？
Are you okay?
你要我打119吗？
Do you want me to call 911?
我喜欢这辆车
I like this car.
你要做…
What are you…
（连线）
（连接资料库）
（洛城联合校区）
（优先目标）
银色凌志 请减速
You, in the silver Lexus. Slow down.
立刻减速停车
Slow down and pull over immediately.
（性感是什么？维多利亚的秘密）
你知道你开多快吗？
Lady, have you any idea how fast you were going?
行照和驾照
Let me see your license and registration.
我喜欢你的枪
I like your gun.
什么？
What?
这玩意坏了
This stupid thing's not working.
怎么了？
What's wrong with this thing?
我讨厌机器
I hate machines.
- 喂？- 凯蒂 是爸爸
- Hello? - Kate, it's your father.
你又要放我鸽子了
You're blowing me off again.
抱歉 我这周末很想见你
I'm so sorry. You know how much I wanted to see you this weekend.
- 只是电脑出状况…- 我知道 你不能多说
- We're having computer problems…- I know, you can't talk about it.
只是…
It's just…
史考特很想见到你
…Scott was really looking forward to this.
我也想多认识他 是真的
Katie. I wish I had more time to get to know him. I really do.
没关系 你在婚礼上一定会见到他
That's okay. You're bound to run into him at the wedding.
拜托 我还不肯接受这事实
Please. I'm still in a state of denial about that.
- 我也一样 - 嘿 凯蒂
- You're not the only one. - Hey, kiddo.
你不需要我对他的意见
You don't need me to pass judgment on this guy.
你一向都很独立自主
You've done the right thing your whole life.
你从来就没犯过错
You won't mak e a mistak e. You never do.
我是世上最幸运的父亲
I'm the luckiest father in the world, you know?
我从来不必替女儿担心害怕
I've never had to be afraid for my daughter.
我得走了 带他来找我 我保证不会爽约
Listen, I hate this. I gotta run. Come see me. I promise I won't cancel.
我们会去的
We will.
- 再见 我爱你 - 我也爱你
- Bye, Dad, I love you. - Love you too.
- 什么状况？- 新的电脑病毒威力强大
- Okay, what have we got? - This new computer virus is tricky.
它感染一半民间网路 以及次要军事电脑程式
It's infected half the civilian Internet as well as secondary military apps.
- 薪俸 库存管理系统 - 主要防御系统呢？
- Payroll, inventory. - Primary defence nets are still clean?
目前防火墙还很牢固
So far the firewalls are holding up.
五角大厦要我们用人工智慧…
Sir, the Pentagon has proposed we use our Al to scan the infrastructure.
扫瞄系统核心并消灭病毒
Search and destroy for any hint of the virus.
这就像是用火箭炮打苍蝇
I know, Tony, but that's like going after a fly with a bazooka.
只要几分钟时间就搞定
Once the connection's made, it should only be a few minutes.
但是我们会让一个电脑系统
During which we put everything
控制国防卫星和核弹
under the control of one computer system.
这是史上最聪明的电脑
The most intelligent system ever conceived.
我还是宁愿让人来操控电脑
I still prefer to keep humans in the loop.
还不能启用天网
I'm not sure Skynet's ready.
是 长官
Yes, sir.
谢了
Thanks.
（动物医院兽医专用镇静剂）
（沙漠之星酒吧）
你应该走后门
You're supposed to go around to the back.
（不符合）
我叫你走…
Hey, I said you're supposed to go…
（淑女之夜）
（不适宜）
（符合）
- 把衣服脱光 - 别这么猴急嘛
- Take off your clothes. - Patience, honey.
臭婊子 还没轮到你
Bitch. Wait your turn.
- 脱光衣服 - 去跟我的手说
- Your clothes. - Talk to the hand.
现在
Now.
（准确）
（吉姆汉堡）
欢迎光临 你要点什么？
Welcome to Jim's Burgers. Can I tak e your order?
- 荷西巴瑞拉？- 我就是
- Jose Barrera? - Yeah, that's me.
（荷西巴瑞拉 符合）
全球网路突然中断…
Growing concern over widespread outages in the global digital network…
谣传出现一个超级病毒
…have prompted rumours of a new computer super-virus.
- 华尔街分析师…- 糟糕 我妈回来了
- Wall Street analysts are confident…- Shit! My mom's home.
把啤酒藏起来 拿去
Here. Hide the beer. Hide the beer. Here. Take that.
快 快…
Go, go, go.
伊莉莎白和威廉安德森？
Elizabeth and William Anderson?
我是威廉 我姐在楼上 有事吗？
I'm Bill. My sister's upstairs. Is there something wrong?
怎么回事？
What's going on?
有急事 我要到诊所
I have to go to the clinic. It's an emergency.
现在是凌晨四点半
It's 4:30 in the morning.
你起床前我就会回来
Well, I'll be back before you get up.
别叫了 是我
Cool it, guys, it's just me.
有一只病猫要来
We've got a sick cat coming in.
这下好了
Great.
吸毒者
Junkies.
请你别报警
Please, don't do that.
我猜上礼拜也是你干的
I suppose it was you who ripped us off last week.
把电话放下来
Put the phone down.
对不起
Sorry.
我只是…
I just…
需要一些药
I needed some medicine.
半里外有一家急诊医院
There's an emergency clinic half a mile away.
我不能去
Can't do that.
你吃了多少药？
How much did you take?
- 够多了 - 这是…
- Enough. - Well…
用来把公狗阉掉的药
…this is the stuff we use to chemically neuter dogs.
你自己看
Take a look.
喂！
Hey!
别把我关起来
Jesus! You didn't have to do that!
下次学聪明点 别用漆弹枪
Next time bring a clue, not a paintball gun.
- 我不是坏人 - 才怪
- No, this isn't what you think. - Yeah, right.
小黑得了肺炎他一直咳个不停
I think Hercules has got pneumonia. He started coughing and won't stop.
- 诊所出了点问题 - 我的猫得了急病耶
- Betsy, I've got a problem in the back. - A problem? This is an emergency!
- 他听起来像是吞了毛球 - 我会不知道吗？
- It sounds like a hairball. - I know what a hairball sounds like.
- 孟医生呢？- 凌晨五点半
- Where's Dr. Monroe? - It's 5:30 in the morning.
他还在睡觉 有必要我会请他来
I'm sure he's home sleeping. He'll come in if he has to.
带小黑进去等我几分钟
Just wait in here with Hercules and I'll be a few minutes, all right?
柯麦克的地下室
Mike Kripke's basement.
什么？什么意思？
What? What does that mean?
你是约翰康纳
You're John Connor.
我是凯蒂布斯特
I'm Kate Brewster.
我们是西丘国中同学
We went to West Hills Junior High together.
- 不是吧 - 你发生什么事？
- Jesus. - What happened to you, John?
国二那年你突然消失无踪
Middle of eighth grade, you just disappeared.
你的养父母又出事
And there was that thing about your foster parents.
他们惨遭谋杀
Yeah, they were murdered.
不是我杀的
I didn't do it.
搞什么？
What the hell?
你有同伴吗？
Is somebody with you?
凯萨琳布斯特？
Katherine Brewster?
不是
No.
（分析遗传基因）
（主要目标：约翰康纳）
约翰康纳来过 他去了哪里？
John Connor was here. Where did he go?
快说 他去了哪里？
Tell me. Where did he go?
凯萨琳布斯特？
Katherine Brewster?
把我放下来
What are you doing? Let me down!
快把我放下来
Let me down! Let me down!
约翰康纳呢？
Where is John Connor?
我说了你就放我走？
If I tell you, will you let me go?
对
Yes.
他…
He's…
被我关在狗笼
…in the kennel, in a cage.
你说你要放我走
You said that you'd let me go.
我说谎
I lied.
求求你 你要放我走
Please, please, please. You have to let me go!
约翰康纳
John Connor.
时候到了
It is time.
你要来杀我？
You here to kill me?
不 你要活下去
No. You must live.
你来干嘛？
Why are you here?
- 我们要去哪儿？- 继续逃亡
- Where are we going? - Keep moving.
快逃吧
Get out of here.
快点
Now!
- 没有脉搏 - 把他抬下来
- No pulse. - See if you can get him down.
不行
I can't.
他重得要命
This guy weighs a ton.
- 911 - 我被绑架了
- 911. - Yes. Yes. I'm being kidnapped.
- 你在哪里？- 不知道 在货车上
- Where are you now? - I don't know where. I'm in my truck.
一辆丰田货车
It's a Toyota Tundra.
车身有艾氏动物医院的名字 我被关在后面
It says " Emery Animal Hospital" on the side. I'm locked inside the back.
喂？
Hello?
（讯号中断）
可恶！
Shit! Shit!
（遥控行车）
下来
Get off.
让我下车
Let me out!
你在这儿干嘛？
What are you doing here?
还不都是你害的
You tell me. You got me into this.
- 停车 - 不行
- Stop the car. - I can't. Not yet.
- 混球 快停车 - 闭嘴
- You bastard! Stop the car! - Shut up!
王八蛋
Son of a bitch.
该死
Goddamn it.
看你干的好事
Look what you did to my car.
这是公司车耶 混蛋
This is my company car, asshole.
给我滚下车
Get your ass out here.
马上滚下来
Get your ass out of the car. Now!
你在干嘛？
What are you doing?
你没保险我就要海扁你
If you don't have insurance, I'm gonna rip your balls off.
- 我不想惹麻烦 - 闭嘴！
- I don't want any problems, okay? - Shut up!
救命啊
Help!
谁在后面？怎么回事？
Who's talking back there? What's going on?
- 冷静点 - 闭嘴
- Calm down. - Shut up!
- 我被绑架了 快报警 - 正如我所料
- I'm being kidnapped! Call the police! - Well, I'll be goddamned.
- 快报警！- 哇塞 警察来得还真快
- Call 911! - A cop when you need one.
快放我出来
Help, please! Please!
Let me out of here! Help!
你给我滚回来 混蛋！
Get back here, asshole!
那是警察 你要停车
That's the cops! You have to pull over!
我会停车才怪
Yeah, first chance I get.
（锁定目标）
坐好了
Hold on!
快停车
Stop it!
我来开
I'll drive.
下去
Get out.
对不起
Excuse me.
（目标距离）
坐过去
Move over.
没有脑震荡的症状
No sign of brain trauma.
我很好 谢了
Yeah, I'm fine, thanks.
你记得我吗？
Do you even remember me?
莎拉康纳 赛博坦公司
Sarah Connor? Blowing up Cyberdyne?
后会有期吧 宝贝 记得吗？
"Hasta la vista, baby." Ring any bells?
那是另一个魔鬼终结者
That was a different T-101.
你们是工厂制造的？
What, do you come off an assembly line or something?
没错
Exactly.
我又得重新教你一次
Oh, man. I'm gonna have to teach you everything all over again.
凯萨琳布斯特 你有没有受伤？
Katherine Brewster, have you sustained injury?
去死吧 混蛋
Drop dead, you asshole!
恕难从命
I'm unable to comply.
你要带我去哪儿？
Where are you taking me?
安全的地方
To a safe location.
下一个交流道放她走
All right, get off at the next exit. Let her out.
不行 我要保护凯萨琳布斯特
Negative. Katherine Brewster must be protected.
- 他们是来找我的 - 他们找不到你
- I thought they were after me. - You could not be located.
才派TX除掉你的手下
So a T-X was sent back through time to eliminate your lieutenants.
她也会加入反抗军？
So she's gonna be in the Resistance?
你根本不该存在
No, no. No, you shouldn't even exist.
赛博坦公司十年前被毁了
I mean, we took out Cyberdyne over 10 years ago.
- 我们阻止了审判日 - 只是拖延时间
- We stopped Judgment Day. - You only postponed it.
审判日一定会来临
Judgment Day is inevitable.
我需要切割工具
I require a cutting tool.
握好方向盘
Here, take the wheel.
- 你在干嘛？- 我身上有两枚氢电池
- What are you doing? - I am powered by hydrogen fuel cells.
其中一枚受损
My primary cell was damaged by a plasma attack.
TX是战斗机器人 身上有电浆反应器…
T-X is designed for extreme combat, driven by a plasma reactor…
和多种武器
…and equipped with onboard weapons.
其中包括…
Its arsenal includes…
纳米科技注射器
…nanotechnological transjectors.
- 什么东东？- 她可以控制其它的机器
- Meaning? - It can control other machines.
她的外壳很坚固 足以承受任何攻击
Its body chassis is heavily armoured and hardened to withstand attack.
- 但是你能对付她 - 不能
- You'll find a way to destroy her. - Unlikely.
我是过时的型号
I'm an obsolete design.
TX更快 更强 更聪明
T-X is faster, more powerful and more intelligent.
她是最有效的杀人机器
It's a far more effective killing machine.
这下可好了
Oh, great.
棒透了
That's great.
他们知道我会出现
My presence in this timeline has been anticipated.
TX可以摧毁任何机器人
T-X is designed to terminate other cybernetic organisms.
她是魔鬼终结者的终结者啰？
So she's an anti-Terminator Terminator?
你在吓唬我
You've gotta be shitting me.
我没有吓唬你
No, I am not shitting you.
氢电池受损后非常不稳定
When ruptured, the fuel cells become unstable.
放心
Relax.
- 放我出去 - 别叫了
- Let me out of here! - Relax!
（24小时便利商店）
（收讯中断）
（请稍候）
（电脑当机 恕不刷卡）
真奇怪
Man, this is wack.
每一台都收不到讯号
It's been like this for hours. Every goddamn station.
喂
Hey.
你付不付钱？
Hey! Are you gonna pay for that?
去跟我的手说吧
Talk to the hand.
救命啊 救命啊…
Help! Help me!
救命啊！
Help!
我们快走吧
I think we better go.
牛肉干？
Jerky?
你要绑架我
You're kidnapping me.
- 听着…- 你一向都是问题少年
- Look…- God, you were always a delinquent.
现在还以为耍坏这招很酷
And look at you now, sitting there like the bad-boy thing still works.
你是古惑仔吗？
What are you, some kind of gang member?
你到底有没有良心？
How do you live with yourself?
干嘛？
What?
跟她说我是谁
Tell her who I am.
约翰康纳是全球反抗军领袖…
John Connor is leader of the Worldwide Resistance…
也是人类的救星
…and last hope of humankind.
才怪 他咧？
Right. And him?
他是来自未来的机器人
He's a robot from the future.
外面是肌肤 里面是钢架 他回来保护我
Living tissue over a metal skeleton, sent back in time to protect me.
去死吧
Go to hell.
他对你没有恶意
He doesn't mean you any harm.
我有未婚夫
I have a fiance
他会来找我
He's gonna be looking for me.
你到底想要什么？
What is it that you want?
试着…
Just…
想想看…
…imagine…
假如你知道你会做一件大事
…if you knew you were gonna do something important with your life.
一件惊天动地的大事
Something amazing.
这也许是史上最重要的事
Maybe the most important thing anyone has ever done.
但是有一个问题
But there's a catch.
一定会发生可怕的事
Something terrible has to happen.
你必须…
You couldn't…
试着阻止它发生…
…live with yourself if you didn't try to stop it, but…
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
你这一辈子过的生活…
It's just…The life you know…
你视为理所当然的一切…
…all the stuff that you take for granted…
不会永远存在
…it's not gonna last.
柯麦克
Mike Kripke.
你为什么说柯麦克的地下室？
Back there, why did you say "Kripke's basement"?
那是因为…
Because Mike Kripke's house…
青少年都到柯麦克家亲热 对不对？
…that's where the kids used to go make out, right?
你跟我 我们有没有？
So you and me…Wait, did we…
哇靠 我们有耶
Holy shit, we did.
我们亲热过 你竟然会记得
We made out in Kripke's basement. I cannot believe you remembered that.
你一定是煞到我
I must have made some kind of impression.
别臭美了
Give me a break.
隔天你就上新闻我才会记得
I only remembered because the next day you were in the news.
等等 我遇到他前一天跟你在一起
Wait a second. You and me hooked up the day before I first met him.
过了十年后又在一起
And now again, 10 years later.
你是说我们注定要见面
We were supposed to meet.
这只是巧合
Coincidence.
对呀
Yeah.
你是刚回来吗？
Honey? Did you just get in?
我是艾警探 这是贝警探
Hi, I'm Detective Edwards, L.A.P.D. This is Detective Bell.
凯萨琳布斯特在吗？
We're looking for Katherine Brewster. Is she here?
不在
No.
- 你是她未婚夫史考特？- 是的
- You're her fiance Scott Mason? - Yes.
她工作的动物医院出了事
There was an incident at the veterinary hospital where she works.
她可能身陷危险
We're concerned something may have happened to her.
她人呢？
Where is she?
魏特谷加油站员工报案说…
We got a report from a gas station attendant near Victorville…
他目睹绑票案 这可能有关联
…about a possible kidnapping and it might be related.
我会帮你找到她
I'll help you find her.
跟我来
Come with me.
走吧
Go.
你母亲？
Your mother?
我不知道她葬在这儿
I never even knew where she was buried.
她一死我就逃亡
I hit the road the day she died.
（莎拉康纳 1959-1997 命运要靠自己创造）
你为什么带我来？
Why did you bring me here?
你在干嘛？
No! What are you doing?
住手
Hey, stop!
把你的手拿开！住手！
Get away from it! Stop!
莎拉康纳在墨西哥火化
Sarah Connor was cremated in Mexico.
她的骨灰被撒在大海
Her friends scattered her ashes in the sea.
她的遗愿是把武器藏在这儿
They stored these weapons in accordance with her will.
她是怎么死的？
What happened to her?
血癌
Leukaemia.
很遗憾
I'm sorry.
她发病时我们人在巴哈
We were living in Baja when she was diagnosed.
医生说她只能活半年
They only gave her six months.
但是她却撑了三年
But she fought for three years.
她要确定一件事
Long enough to make sure.
什么事？
To make sure?
世界末日没有来临
That the world didn't end.
她说：「之后的每一天都很宝贵」
" Every day after this one is a gift."
「我们成功了 我们自由了」
She told me, "We made it. We're free."
但是我一直都不相信
But I never really believed that.
我猜她也不相信
I guess she didn't either.
我这一生只能把你当成父亲
You know you were about the closest thing to a father I ever had?
很可怜吧？
How pathetic is that?
给我让开
Out of my way!
我的任务是保护你
My mission is to protect you.
别过来
That's enough.
我发誓我会向你开枪
Move or I'll do it! I swear I will! I'll shoot you!
你开了枪就知道
Go ahead. See what happens.
别向我开枪
Don't do that.
天啊
Oh, my God.
这是警察 你们被包围了
This is the police. We have the building surrounded.
把人质放走
Release your hostage!
别管我 你找的不是我 你在浪费时间
Just leave me here. I'm not the one you want. You're wasting your time.
不对 约翰康纳率领反抗军获得胜利
Incorrect. John Connor leads the Resistance to victory.
怎么会？
How?
为什么是我？
Why? Why me?
因为你是约翰康纳
You are John Connor.
我从小就被我妈灌输这种屁话
Christ, my mom fed me that bullshit since the cradle.
看看我 我不是什么领袖
Look at me. I'm no leader, I never was!
以后也不会是
I'm never gonna…
放手
Let go.
你说的对 我找的不是你
You're right. You're not the one I want.
我在浪费时间
I'm wasting my time.
去你的 你这臭机器人
Fuck you, you fucking machine!
这才像话
Better.
你刚才在耍我？
Oh, you were just dicking with me?
愤怒比绝望更有用
Anger is more useful than despair.
什么？
What?
我的副程式包括人类心理学
Basic psychology is among my subroutines.
还没抓到嫌犯？
Perps still holed up?
了解
Gotcha.
好消息 你未婚妻没事了
Good news. Your fiance's okay.
她人在哪儿？
Where is she?
绿茵墓园 五号公路旁
Greenlawn Cemetery, up off the 5 freeway.
就在沙漠旁边 他们要带她…
It's right by the desert. But they're gonna bring her back to the…
我的老天
Oh, my God! Oh, my dear Jesus! God!
你安全了 不会受伤害
You're safe now. They can't hurt you.
凯蒂 我是西伯曼医生
Kate, my name is Dr. Silberman.
我是警方的创伤后心理顾问
I'm a post-trauma counsellor for the sheriff's department.
你有什么感觉？
How are you feeling?
他不是人
He's not human.
他真的 不是人
He's really not human.
我知道被挟持为人质的感受
I know what it's like to be in a hostage situation.
我也当过人质
I've been there myself.
极度恐惧 心跳加速
The fear, the adrenaline.
都会让人产生各种幻觉
You find yourself imagining things.
不可能发生的事
Impossible things.
疯狂的事
Crazy things.
令人抓狂的事
Insane things.
多年后才能复元
Take years to get over it.
- 上！上！- 进去
- Go, go, go! - Move it!
放下武器！
Drop your weapon!
还有那具棺材！
And the coffin!
向他开枪
Take him down! Take him down!
（发射760枚子弹 17辆车被毁）
（无人伤亡）
继续开枪
Resume fire!
我们要找到凯萨琳布斯特
We must reacquire Katherine Brewster.
她为什么这么重要？
Why? What makes her so goddamn important?
你要透过她联络美国军方…
Through her, you contact remnants of the military…
学会如何对抗天网系统 并组成反抗军核心
…and learn how to fight Skynet, forming the core of the Resistance.
你们的小孩也会很重要
Later, your children will become important.
- 什么？- 她是你的妻子
- What? - She's your wife.
快上来
Get in!
你不想死就快上车
Do you want to live? Come on!
- 那是史考特 怎么可能？- 你的未婚夫？
- It was Scott! How could it be Scott? - Your fiance
TX能化身为任何形体
The T-X is polymimetic, able to take the form of anything it touches.
你的未婚夫死了
Your fiance is dead.
天啊
Oh, my God!
快想办法
Do something!
趴下来
Get down.
我们需要一辆新车
We need a new vehicle.
（主要武器损毁）
（寻找替代品）
（选择替代武器）
别哭了
Hey, come on.
我们要逃下去
We gotta keep moving.
她因为我杀了史考特
She killed Scott because of me.
我知道这么说没什么用…
Look, I know this won't help…
但是有时候我们无法改变事实
…but sometimes things happen that we just can't change.
这不是你的错
It's not your fault.
你确定吗？
Are you sure about this?
我是说我跟她
About her and me, I mean.
你的问题没有道理 她是正值繁殖期的健康女性
Your confusion is not rational. She's a healthy female of breeding age.
当夫妻不是这么简单
There's more to it than that.
我并没有人类两性关系的资料
My database does not encompass the dynamics of human pair bonding.
女魔鬼终结者要杀多少人？
So this Terminatrix, how many others does she have on her hit list?
22人 伊莉莎白和威廉安德森
Twenty-two. Anderson, Elizabeth. Anderson, William.
荷西巴瑞拉 劳勃布斯特
Barrera, Jose. Brewster, Robert.
我父亲？
My father?
既然她没除掉主要目标…
Having failed to acquire its primary target…
就会寻找次要目标
…T- X will resume its default program.
- 她也要去杀我爸？- 很有可能
- She's gonna kill my father too? - There's a high probability.
- 不 - 他是做什么的？
- No. - Who is he? What does he do?
他在空军负责秘密武器系统 我也不清楚
He's in the Air Force. Weapon design, secret stuff. I don't know, exactly.
劳勃布斯特负责制造CRS…
General Robert Brewster is program director of CRS…
也就是电脑研究系统 自主性武器
…Cyber Research Systems, autonomous weapons division.
天网 你说的是天网
Skynet. You're talking about Skynet.
天网是他负责的一种防御系统
Skynet is one of the digital defence systems developed under Brewster.
天啊
Oh, God.
当然了
Oh, my God. Of course.
我终于明白了
It all makes sense now.
如果你当年没回来改变一切…
If you hadn't come back when I was a kid, changed everything…
我就会跟她在一起 也会认识她父亲
…we would have gotten together then. I would have met her father.
- 你不懂吗？- 我不懂
- Don't you see? - I don't understand.
这一切都跟你爸有关
Your father. This is all about your father.
他一直都是关键人物
He's the key. He always was.
你爸才能摧毁天网
Your father is the one who can shut Skynet down.
只有他才办得到
He's the only one who ever could.
我们要在TX之前找到他
We have to get to him before the T-X does.
不行 我不能违反任务
Negative. I cannot jeopardize my mission.
你的任务是拯救人类
This is your mission, to save people!
我的任务是保护你跟她
My mission is to ensure the survival of John Connor and Katherine Brewster.
我要命令你
I am giving you an order.
我不必服从你的命令
I am not programmed to follow your orders.
- 核战爆发后…- 核战？
- After the nuclear war, you both…- Nuclear war?!
不会有核战 我们能阻止它
There doesn't have to be a war! We can stop it!
来不及了
There is insufficient time.
第一枚核弹于6时18分发射
The first launch sequences will be initiated at 6: 18 p.m.
- 今天吗？- 正确
- What, today? - Affirmative.
他在说什么？
John, what is he saying?
审判日
Judgment Day.
世界末日
The end of the world.
三个小时后
It's today, three hours from now.
2小时53分钟
Two hours and 53 minutes.
我们要到墨西哥躲避核爆威力
We must continue south into Mexico to escape the primary blast zones.
不 我们要去找她爸
No, we have to get to her dad.
核爆后摩哈比沙漠首当其冲
The Mojave area will sustain significant nuclear fallout.
你活不了
You will not survive.
你要我躲起来让核战爆发？
You mean we go hide somewhere in a hole while the bombs fall?
这是你的命运
It is your destiny.
- 去我的命运 - 约翰
- Fuck my destiny. - John.
你不能自我终结
You cannot self-terminate.
你不能 我想怎样都行
No, you can't. I can do whatever I want.
我是人 不是机器人
I'm a human being. I'm not some goddamn robot.
- 我是一个电脑有机体 - 随便啦
- Cybernetic organism. - Whatever!
如果我不能劝她爸摧毁天网…
Either we get her father to shut Skynet down…
阻止核战发生 伟大的约翰康纳也不必活
…stop this shit from ever happening, or so much for the great John Connor.
因为我从来都不想要这种命运
Because your future, my destiny, I don't want any part of it. I never did.
根据你的瞳孔大小和体温…
Based on your pupil dilation, skin temperature and motor functions…
你有八成三的可能不会扣扳机
…I calculate an 83? probability that you will not pull the trigger.
听他的话 你一定要救我爸
Please do what he says. You have to save my father!
我估计一小时后可以抵达…
We can reach CRS in approximately one hour…
这要看交通状况
…depending on traffic conditions.
我打不通
I can't get a line.
完全收不到讯号
The whole cell network is down.
天网控制全球通讯…
Skynet is assuming control over global communications…
准备发动攻击
…in preparation for its attack.
这是一场人类与机器的战争…
So if this war is between people and machines…
你为何站在我们这边？
…why are you on our side?
反抗军抓到我 改写我的程式
The Resistance captured me and reprogrammed my CPU.
我原来负责刺杀行动
I was originally designed for assassination missions.
所以…
So…
你不在乎这项任务成功或失败
…you don't really care if this mission succeeds or not.
我们死了对你有什么影响？
If we get killed, does that mean anything to you?
你们死了我就失去功用
If you were to die, I will become useless.
我也没有存在的理由
There will be no reason for me to exist.
谢谢你帮助我们
Thank you for doing this.
你不必谢我
Your gratitude is not required.
我必须服从你的命令
I am programmed to follow your commands.
她的命令？
Her commands?
她改写我的程式…
Katherine Brewster had me reactivated…
派我回到过去
…and sent through the time displacement field.
我在未来扮演什么角色？
What exactly am I in this future of yours?
你是约翰的妻子和副指挥官
You're John Connor's spouse and second-in-command.
不是吧
No, l…
什么？
What?
你糟透了
You're a mess.
你也不是我喜欢的那一型
Hey, you're not exactly my type, either.
我为什么不派你来？
Why didn't I send you back?
我不能回答你的问题
I am not authorized to answer your question.
- 他为什么没派你来？- 他死了
- Why didn't he send you back? - He was dead.
衰毙了
Well, that sucks.
- 人都难逃一死 - 我知道
- Humans inevitably die. - Yeah, I know.
我是怎么…算了
So how does it… No.
也许我不想知道
Maybe I don't want to know.
他是怎么死的？
How does he die?
他在2032年7月4日遇害
John Connor was terminated on July 4th, 2032.
他小时候被我这种型号救过
I was selected for the emotional attachment he had for my model…
所以他对我有感情 这对我的任务有帮助
…due to his boyhood experiences. This aided in my infiltration.
你在说什么呀？
What are you saying?
我杀了你
I killed you.
这一定搞错了 主要军事系统都没问题
This has to be a mistake. As of 1100, all military systems were secure.
只有民间系统受病毒感染 网路 飞航局和发电厂
They were. Only the civilian sector was affected. Internet, air traffic.
但是现在空军基地也这样
Minutes ago, guidance computers at Vandenberg crashed.
看来是病毒搞的鬼
We thought it was an error. It looks like the virus.
阿拉斯加预警系统也失效
Early warning in Alaska is down.
国防卫星讯号受到干扰
Satellite signals are scrambled.
飞弹基地和核子潜艇呢？
What about the missile silos, the subs?
失去联络
We've lost contact.
天啊 我们毫无防御力
You're saying this country is completely open to attack.
理论上我们可能正遭到攻击
Theoretically, we could be under attack already.
这是谁干的？敌国或是电脑骇客？
Who's doing this? A foreign power or some computer hacker in his garage?
我们追踪不到病毒来源
We can't trace the virus or pin it down.
它好像有意识 一直在成长
It keeps growing and changing, like it has a mind of its own.
不可能
This can't be happening.
参谋总长从五角大厦来电
The Pentagon's on the secure line. It's the chairman.
好吧
All right.
听着…
Look…
这一切都不会发生
…none of this is gonna happen.
我们找到你爸 请他摧毁天网 核战就不会爆发
We get to your dad, get him to pull the plug on Skynet. The bombs won't fall.
他以后也不必杀我
He won't have to kill me someday.
他根本不会存在
He'll never even exist.
我跟你从此分道扬镳
You and I, we can just go our separate ways.
你知道吗 柯麦克的地下室…
You know, Mike Kripke's basement…
那是我的初吻
That was the first time I ever kissed a guy.
真的吗？
Really?
男女调情是件好事
Your levity is good.
能消除紧张情绪和恐惧感
It relieves tension and the fear of death.
我们希望你有解决方案
We're hoping you have a solution for us.
天网还不能进行系统连线
I know, sir, but Skynet is not ready for a system- wide connection.
民间包商可不是这么说
That's not what your civilian counterparts there told me.
他们说我们可以消灭病毒
They say we can stop this damn virus.
我知道你怕表现不好…
I understand there's a certain amount of performance anxiety…
不过你的手下说只要启动天网…
…but your boys say if we plug Skynet into all of our systems…
就能杀死病毒 让我控制军队
…it'll squash this thing and give me back control of my military.
请你听我说
Mr. Chairman, I need to make myself very clear.
天网一连线就会控制军方
If we uplink now, Skynet will be in control of your military.
但是你能控制天网 对吧？
But you'll be in control of Skynet, right?
没错
That is correct, sir.
那就去做吧
Then do it.
这件事一旦成功…
And, Brewster, if this thing works…
你就有用不完的资金
…you'll get all the funding you'll ever need.
是 长官
Yes, sir.
（连线）
（执行 是/否？）
长官？
Sir?
要我来吗？
Shall I?
不
No.
这是我的责任
It's my job now.
- 天网防御系统启动 - 我们进去了
- Skynet Defence System activated. - We're in.
穿过防火墙 进入防御系统和潜舰
We're past the firewalls, local defence nets, Minutemen, subs.
天网以每秒六十兆次浮点运算
Skynet's fully operational, processing at 60 teraflops a second.
它在一分钟内就能杀死病毒
It should take less than a minute to find the virus and kill it.
祈祷上帝它有效
Let's pray to God this works.
停电吗？
Power failure?
我不知道是怎么回事
No. I don't know what it is.
到底发生什么事？
What the hell is going on?
爸爸
Daddy!
凯蒂 你跑来干嘛？
What are you doing here?
爸 快躲开
Daddy! Get away from it!
小心
Watch out!
爸 别动
Daddy, don't move.
她一定会回来
She'll be back.
我们要关掉天网
We have to shut down Skynet.
它的系统核心在哪里？
Where's the system core? In this building?
天网被电脑病毒感染
Skynet. The virus has infected Skynet.
天网就是病毒 它控制了一切
Skynet is the virus! It's why everything's falling apart!
天网产生自觉性
Skynet has become self-aware.
一小时后就会向敌人发射核弹
In one hour it will initiate a massive nuclear attack on its enemy.
什么敌人？
What enemy?
我们！
Us!
人类！
Humans.
天啊 机器开始反扑了
Oh, God! It's the machines. They're starting to take over.
我们要到我的办公室
My office, on this floor, we have to get there.
密码在我的保险柜
The access codes are in my safe.
它们为什么滥杀人类？
Why are they killing everyone?
为了消灭对所有天网潜在的威胁
To destroy any threat to Skynet.
密码在哪里？
Which ones are the codes?
红色信封
Red envelope.
你们一定要赶到水晶峰
Crystal Peak. You have to get to Crystal Peak.
- 他在说什么？- 水晶峰
- What is he saying? - Crystal Peak.
位于内华达山脉的堡垒
A hardened facility in the Sierra Nevada mountains.
方位015度 东北52英里
Fifty-two miles northeast, bearing 0.5 degrees.
系统核心在那儿？
That's the system core?
那是唯一的机会
It's your only chance.
你们需要一架飞机 顺着粒子加速器就会到跑道
You'll need a plane. The particle accelerator leads to the runway.
好好照顾我女儿
Take care of my daughter.
凯蒂 对不起
Oh, Katie, I am sorry.
我打开了潘朵拉魔盒
I opened Pandora's box.
快趴下
Get down!
你也救不了他 来吧
There's nothing you can do. Come on.
你们快走 这里不安全
We must go. It is not safe here.
凯蒂 走吧
Kate, we have to go.
他要你跟我走
Kate! He wanted you to come with me.
他要我们摧毁天网 来吧
He wanted us to shut Skynet down. Come on.
走吧
Come on.
快跑
Run!
走吧
Let's go.
那儿 跟着走就会到跑道
That's it. We can follow it out to the runway.
来吧
Come on.
怎么了？
What?
没事
Nothing.
你让我想起我妈
You remind me of my mother.
天啊 她追来了
Oh, God. She's coming.
你在干嘛？
What are you doing?
启动加速器
Powering up.
来吧
Come on.
（5.76兆瓦特）
（启动电磁场）
成功了
It's working.
去死吧 贱货
Just die, you bitch!
走吧
Come on.
我爸的飞机 我会开
There's my father's plane. I trained on it.
太好了 他赶来了
Yes! He made it.
离我远一点
Get away from me.
快走
Leave!
快点！
Now!
走吧
Let's go!
- 主开关 油门杆 - 走吧
- The master's on. Throttle's set. - Come on. Let's go.
求求你 你不能杀我
Oh, please. You can't do this.
我别无选择
I have no choice.
TX…
The T-X…
侵入我的系统
…has corrupted my system.
你说过 你不能杀害人类
You can't kill a human being. You said so yourself.
放开他
Let him go!
（主要目标）
你可以抗拒
You're fighting it right now.
我的中央处理器很完整
My CPU is intact.
但是我无法控制其它功能
But I cannot control my other functions.
你不必杀我 你不想杀我
You don't have to do this. You don't want to do this!
这跟我的想法无关
Desire is irrelevant.
我只是个机器人
I am a machine.
你的任务是什么？
What is your mission?
保护约翰康纳和…
To ensure the survival of John Connor…
凯萨琳布斯特
…and Katherine Brewster.
你的任务就要失败了
You are about to fail that mission!
我办不到
I can…I cannot.
你知道该怎么做
You know what you have to do.
你也知道我的命运
You know my destiny.
（执行 放弃）
我一定要活下去
I have to live.
（指令无效）
- 你没事吧？- 怎么回事？
- Are you okay? - What happened?
他下不了手 把自己关掉了
He couldn't do it. He shut himself down.
- 你能开吗？- 可以
- Can you fly? - Yeah.
015度…
Okay. 015 degrees…
52英里 最高时速160英里
…52 miles, our max air speed is about 160.
只剩32分钟
We've got 32 minutes.
一定要成功
It's just you and me now.
要是不成功呢？
What if we can't stop it?
这些炸药能毁灭十台超级电脑
There's enough C-4 here to take out 10 supercomputers.
我们一定会成功
We're gonna make it, Kate.
人类的未来都靠我们了
The future is up to us.
一定是那儿
That's gotta be it.
（重新启动）
（危险）
（军事要地 禁止进入）
天网 也许还有机器人
Skynet. There may be more of them.
来吧
Come on.
这是一道防爆门
I think this is some kind of blast door.
谁也炸不进去
There's no way we can blow through this thing.
你看
John, look.
现在怎么办？
Now what?
（蓝478）
这是密码提示
It's a code prompt.
输入达科塔775
Type in " Dakota 775."
（开启电源）
红176
"Red 176."
我们要把门打开
Come on! We gotta get this thing open.
这里 是「亚维隆412」
Here. It's "Avalon 412."
快输入呀！
Put it in!
（准许进入）
来吧！
Come on!
我回来了
I'm back.
（失败）
快去吧
Go! Now!
快点
Come on!
- 谢谢你 - 我们会再见面
- Thank you. - We'll meet again.
快去吧
Go!
来吧
Come on!
你被终结了
You are terminated.
搭电梯
The elevator.
我设定五分钟后引爆
I'll set the detonator for five minutes.
时间足够让我们上去
That should give us enough time to get back up.
这是什么地方？
What is this place?
（美国总统）
这些是三十年前的电脑
These computers are 30 years old.
这不是天网
This isn't Skynet.
这儿什么也没有
There's nothing here.
这是政府官员的避难所
This is a fallout shelter for VIPs.
只是他们没得到任何预警
Only they never got the warning.
可恶
Goddamn it!
什么也没有
There's nothing here!
他为什么不说？
Why didn't he tell us?
他为什么带我们来这里？
Why did he lead us down here?
让我们活下去
To live.
这就是他的任务
That was his mission.
根本就阻止不了核战
There was never any stopping it.
约翰…
John…
我们可以…
…we could just…
让它爆炸
…let it go.
喂？
Hello?
有人听到吗？
Hello? Can somebody hear me?
这是蒙大拿州民防队
This is Montana Civil Defence.
请回答
Somebody please come in.
有人在吗？
Is there anybody there?
有人听到吗？
Anyone reading me? Over.
我们听说发生核战
Rumours about a launch sequence.
但是指挥部完全失联
Command and control have brok en down.
有人听到吗？有人吗？
Is anyone receiving me? Somebody?
请回答
Somebody please come in.
有人在吗？
Anybody out there?
- 空军司令部遭到攻击 - 请回答
- SAC Nellis. We're under attack. - CQ? CQ?
有人在吗？
Is anybody there?
这是水晶峰的约翰康纳
This is John Connor at Crystal Peak.
到底发生什么事？谁是那里的指挥官？
Connor? What the hell is happening? Who's in charge there?
是我
I am.
你能帮助我们吗？
Connor, can you help us?
这是蒙大拿州民防队 你说你在哪里？
This is Montana Civil Defence. Where did you say you were again?
天网产生自觉性之后
By the time Skynet became self-aware…
立刻侵入全球数百万台电脑
…it had spread into millions of computer servers across the planet.
办公室 宿舍…无所不在
Ordinary computers in office buildings, dorm rooms, everywhere.
它存在于软体和网路
It was software in cyberspace.
根本没有系统核心 所以无法关闭
There was no system core. It could not be shut down.
午后6时18分展开攻击 就跟他说的一样
The attack began at 6:18 p.m., just as he said it would.
审判日
Judgment Day.
人类几乎被保护自己的武器…
The day the human race was nearly destroyed…
消灭的一天
…by weapons they'd built to protect themselves.
我早该知道 我们不能阻止这一切
I should have realized our destiny was never to stop Judgment Day.
而是要一起…
It was merely to survive it…
活下去
…together.
魔鬼终结者早就知道了
The Terminator knew.
他试着告诉我们…
He tried to tell us…
但是我不想听
…but I didn't want to hear it.
也许未来已经发生 我不知道
Maybe the future has been written. I don't know.
我只知道魔鬼终结者教导我：
All I know is what the Terminator taught me…
「永远不要停止奋战」
Never stop fighting.
我永远不会放弃
And I never will.
战争才刚开始
The battle has just begun.